https://www.partsforsaabs.com/privacy.php?osCsid=94114c46dbb478c36c2e5ed5ae7c04b6

Currency
All purchases are charged in GBP and prices in other currencies are provided as a guideline only and are subject to fluctuation
Email Us Here
0Item(s)
Saab Parts  >  Privacy & Cookies
Filter Parts By Model RangeMakeSaabModelYearApply Filter  Clear Filter  VIN Number Look Up
×
Saab VIN Look Up
To accurately identify manufacturer specified vehicle model year (which can frequently be different to year of registration), please enter your 17 digit (vehicle identification number) VIN or Chassis number below. This number is generally located at the base of the windscreen, or on the vehicle documents.
Only Suitable for Vehicles 1986 onwards
SubmitSubmit
Filter Parts By Category Accessories/StylingAlloy WheelsBody & TrimBooks & ManualsBraking SystemCar CareClutch & TransmissionCooling SystemElectrical & IgnitionEngine PartsExhaust SystemFuel SystemHeating & VentilationIn Car EntertainmentLighting, Mirrors, BulbsPerformance & TuningSaab GiftsSaab ToolsService ItemsSteering & SuspensionPFS Clearance Items!!
Filter Parts By Manufacturer Please SelectATEAutoglymAvo UKBentley PublishersBilstein SuspensionBlack DiamondBoschBougicordBSRComma Oilsdo88.seEBC BrakesEGREibach SuspensionForge MotorsportGarrettGliptone LeathercareGoodridge BrakelinesGunsonH&R SuspensionHaynes PublishingHirsch PerformanceITG FiltersJetex ExhaustsJR FiltersKilenKoni SuspensionLesjoforsLockheedLucasLUKMagnecorMerrell PublishingMintex BrakingMountneyNEVSNGK Spark PlugsOsram LightingPFSPhilipsPipercrossPowerflex Poly BushesRenovo Roof productsRonal AlloysSaab/GMSachsSamco SportSASSFS PerformanceSKFSuperflex Poly BushesTarox BrakingValeoWP Pro
Privacy & Cookie Information
PartsforSaabs.com knows that you care
how information about you is used and
shared. We appreciate your trust and want you to feel confident in our services
and security as it relates to your personal information. This notice describes
our privacy policy. By visiting PartsforSaabs.com, you are accepting the practices
described in this Privacy Notice.
1) What Personal Information About Customers Does PartsforSaabs.com Gather?
2) What About Cookies?
3) Does PartsforSaabs.com Share the Information It Receives?
4) How Secure Is Information About Me?
5)
Which Information Can I Access?
6)
Conditions of Use, Notices, and Revisions
7)
Information You Give Us
8)
Automatic Information
9)
Questions
What Personal Information About Customers Does PartsforSaabs.com Gather?
- [top]
The information we learn from customers helps us personalise and continually
improve your shopping experience at PartsforSaabs.com. Here are the types
of information we gather.
Information You Give Us: We receive and store any information you
enter on our Web site or give us in any other way. You can choose not to
provide certain information, but then you might not be able to take advantage
of many of our features. We use the information that you provide for such
purposes as responding to your requests, fulfilling orders, customising future
shopping for you, improving our store features, and communication with you.
Automatic Information: We receive and store certain types of information
whenever you interact with our website. For example, like many web sites,
we sometimes use "cookies", these cookies are quite harmless and
are simply used to enable us to provide you with added functionality whilst
on this site, such as storing the contents of your cart as you move from page to page.
E-mail Communications: To help us improve your shopping experience,
we sometimes send you newsletters of our services and products, notifications
of changes to our policies, and
order confirmations and updates. If you do not want to receive e-mail from us, other
than order notifications and receipts, please adjust your "subscription" preferences
by logging into your account.
What About Cookies?
- [top]
Cookies are alphanumeric identifier text files that we transfer to your computers
hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your
browser and to provide features such as storage of items in your Shopping Cart
between visits, or to 'remember' your 'Year, Make & Model' settings (where used) as you change pages within the site. All cookie information set by us is completely anonymous, no information that could personally identify you in any way is ever stored by us in a cookie.
Does PartsforSaabs.com Share the Information It Receives?
- [top]
We respect your privacy and appreciate your business. At no time do we ever
provide your account contact or transaction history to any third party vendor,
associate or service provider unless absolutely neccessary in order to complete
your transaction and order.
How Secure Is Information About Me?
- [top]
We work to protect the security of any personal information
during transmission by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts
information you provide
to us for purchasing of our products or services. To check whether your browser
is using SSL secure encryption you can look for the small 'closed padlock' icon generally
visible in the address bar of your browser or sometimes in the lower right of your browser when at the checkout or when editing any of
your account information. For your added security, PFS Parts Ltd. uses an EV SSL certificate (Extended Validation) , this certificate is only issued after our website and company has been extensively checked. Our EV certificate is clearly visible by means of the green colouration in the address bar.
We use SagePay and/or PayPal to process all credit card transactions placed with us. This means that all of your card details are entered directly into either the SagePay or PayPal website, both of these companies are extremely well established and secure! You need have no worries about your credit card information being compromised in any way when purchasing from us.
At NO time
is your credit card information ever stored on this website, nor any other website or server that we (PFS Parts Ltd.) operate, or in any physical format by PFS Parts Ltd.
Which Information Can I Access?
- [top]
PartsforSaabs.com gives you access to a broad range of information about
your account and your interactions with us for the limited purpose of viewing
and, in certain cases, updating that information.
Conditions of Use, Notices, and Revisions
- [top]
If you choose to visit PartsforSaabs.com, your visit and any dispute over
privacy is subject to this Notice and our Conditions of Use, including limitations
on damages, arbitration of disputes, and application of the law of the United Kingdom.
If you have any concern about the privacy of your personal
information as used and collected within our website, please send us a thorough
description by clicking on the &quotContact Us" link in the menu towards the bottom of the page,
and we will do our best to resolve it.
Our business changes constantly, and our Privacy Notice and the Conditions
of Use will change also. We may e-mail periodic reminders of our notices and
conditions, unless you have instructed us not to, but you should also check our
Web site frequently to see any recent changes. Unless stated otherwise, our current
Privacy Notice applies to all information that we have about you and your account.
We stand behind the promises we make however, and will never materially change
our policies and practices to make them less protective of customer information
collected in the past without the consent of affected customers.
Information You Give Us
- [top]
You provide most such information when you search, buy, order, post reviews,
or other methods of communication via our website or email to PartsforSaabs.com. As a result of those actions, you might supply us with such information
as your name, address, and phone numbers.
Automatic Information
- [top]
For security purposes PartsforSaabs.com sometimes collects and analyzes the
Internet protocol (IP) address used to connect your computer to the Internet,
and to our website. This is done solely for your protection.
Questions
- [top]
Questions regarding our Conditions of Usage, Privacy Policy, or other policy
related material can be directed to our support staff by clicking on the "Contact
Us" link in the
menu towards the bottom of the page.
Continue
Special OffersView all
9-3SS 06'-12' 2.8 V6 models Service Filter Kit - Genuine Saab£86.29£39.99
9-5 98'-10' all 4 cyl Petrol models Service Filter Kit - Genuine Saab£89.08£49.99
9-3 Sports 03' on 2.0 Turbo Petrol - Timing Chain Kit - Genuine Saab£310.33£179.95
-Genuine Saab Timing & Balance Shaft Repair Kit - See Desc for Application£351.60£334.86
Classic 900 85'-93' 4 & 5 speed Clutch - Fast Road (Stage 1)£193.45£178.95
9-3SS 1.9 TiD all 8/16V models - Single Mass Conversion Kit (Stage 3 RACE)£1,024.27£921.84
9-3SS 1.9 TiD all 8/16V models - Single Mass Conversion Kit (Stage 2 +30%)£901.20£811.08
9-3SS 1.9 TiD all 8/16V models - Single Mass Conversion Kit (Stage 1 +20%)£855.05£769.54
NG900 94'-98' Goodridge Brakeline kit£87.10£75.00
9000 85'-98' Goodridge Brakeline kit£87.10£75.00
9-5 98'-10' Goodridge Brakeline kit£130.14£114.95
9-3 98'-02' Goodridge Brakeline kit£87.10£75.00
9-5 02' on Aero & 3.0 V6 models REAR Disc (pair) & Pad Kit - MINTEX£125.59£96.95
9-5 99' on (non Aero or 3.0 V6) REAR Disc (pair) & Pad Kit - MINTEX£109.54£93.95
9-5 99'-10' Aero 308mm FRONT Disc (pair) & Pad Kit - MINTEX£157.09£91.95
9-5 1998 to 2006 3.0 V6 Direct Ignition Cassette£330.21£253.50
9-5 Aero & 3.0 Diesel 99' to 10 308MM 12 Groove Black Diamond FRONT Discs£294.60£229.95
9-3 Viggen 99' to 02' 308MM 12 Groove Black Diamond FRONT Discs & Pads£294.60£229.95
9-3SS 03' on Aero with 292mm REAR discs (Pair) & Pad - Kit MINTEX£108.55£86.95
9-3SS 03' on (Not AERO) 278mm REAR discs (Pair) & Pad - Kit MINTEX£84.56£66.95
9-3SS 03' on Aero 314mm discs FRONT discs (Pair) & Pad - Kit MINTEX£219.53£117.95
9-3SS 03' on Aero with 302mm discs FRONT discs (Pair) & Pad - Kit MINTEX£116.96£86.95
9-3SS 03' on (NOT AERO) 285mm FRONT discs (Pair) & Pad - Kit MINTEX£93.29£78.95
9-3 Sports 03'-07' all models - Black Mesh Chrome Surround Styling Grille£129.82£127.86
9-3SS 03' on (278mm solid discs) - Brake Caliper Rear Right (o/s)£69.99£59.99
9-3SS 03' on (278mm solid discs) - Brake Caliper Rear Left (n/s)£69.99£59.99
NG900 97'-98' FRONT Brake Disc (pair) & Pad - Kit - MINTEX£127.07£78.95
9-5 98' on (NOT AERO) FRONT Disc (pair) & Pad - Kit - MINTEX£127.07£78.95
9-3 98'-02' (NOT VIGGEN) FRONT Disc (pair) & Pad Kit - MINTEX£127.07£78.95
9-5 1998 to 1999 all manual models - Torque Rod (Centre)£78.12£70.31
Convert currencies
Customer Information
About UsShipping & ReturnsGeneral FAQ'sPrivacy & Cookie PolicyTerms & ConditionsDriving DirectionsSite Map
Get In TouchPFS Parts Ltd.
Unit 8 - Saxon Court,
Bradfield Close,
Finedon Road Ind. Est,
Wellingborough,
NN8 4RQ,
United Kingdom
Tel: +44 (0)333 577 9961Calls to 03 numbers cost no more than a national rate call to an 01 or 02 number and must count towards any inclusive minutes in the same way as 01 and 02 calls. These rules apply to calls from any type of line including mobile, BT, other fixed line or payphone. During business hours emails are responded to promptly at no cost. Further details regarding 03 numbers available here.CALL THIS NUMBER HERE
Fax: +44 (0)844 800 2740
Email Us Here
Get the Newsletter:
Sign Up
Secure Payment We accept
PFS Parts Ltd. is a specialist parts company established in 2003. This site offers a 'one-stop' online parts shop for Saab car parts at great prices.
We can supply a huge selection of Saab parts, including genuine Saab parts, aftermarket parts and performance parts. Click for more about PFS Parts...
Copyright © 2020 PartsforSaabs.com
PFS Parts Ltd is an independent supplier of Saab parts and is in no way connected to Saab AB or any of its group companies
